poachable.co 2016-03-08

# 1

                                               STUDIO6, INC.
                                            PRIVACY POLICY
Last Updated: ​   July 15, 2015
Our Commitment to Your Privacy
We at Studio6, Inc. (“Studio6,” “we,” “us,” “our”) know that our users (“you,” “your”) care about how
your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the
following to learn more about our Privacy Policy. By visiting or using the Studio6 websites (including
www.anthology.co​     and any other websites where this Privacy Policy is posted) (the “Sites”) and any other
features, content, mobile and other applications, or any other services we offer from time to time in
connection with the Sites (collectively, the “Services”), in any manner, you acknowledge that you accept
the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy, and you hereby consent that we will collect, use,
and share your information in the following ways. Your privacy matters to us, so please do take the time
to get to know our practices – and if you have any questions, contact us at ​legal@anthology.co​  .
Scope of this Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect on our Services. Our Services may link to or
interoperate with other websites or services over which we have no control. We are not responsible for the
privacy policies or practices of other websites or services. You may wish to review the privacy policies of
those websites and services so you can understand how they collect, use and share your information.
Information We Collect
We collect information about you when you use our Services. For example, depending on the Services
you use and whether you create an account and related profile (“Anthology Account”), we may collect:
    ●    Your name
    ●    Contact information, such as address, email address, telephone number
    ●    Information about your education, occupation, career history, skills and experience, awards,
         memberships and affiliations, activities and interests, including your resume
    ●    Your age, gender, race or ethnicity, if permitted by local law and you choose to provide it
    ●    Information about third parties, such as references or contacts, that you provide to us if you have
         their express written consent to do so
    ●    Information imported by you or your connections from third party applications
    ●    Credit card number and billing information (for services requiring payment)
    ●    Other information requested within your Anthology Account
We automatically collect information about you depending on how you use our Services, the areas of our
Sites that you visit, as well as information about your computer or mobile device, including your IP
address, phone number, device ID, physical location, browser and operating system type, and referring
URLs, using various technological means (including “cookies” and other technologies such as pixel tags
and web beacons, as further described below). This information is necessary for providing personalized
and location­based content as well as for analyzing the use of resources, troubleshooting problems,
                                                       1

preventing fraud, and monitoring and improving our Services. We may combine this information with
information in your Anthology Account to help prevent fraud.
We may collect information about you from publicly­available websites, such as LinkedIn, and we may
also ask you to provide the URL of your LinkedIn profile. We may use the information we collect to
create a profile, even if you do not have a Anthology Account, or append it to your existing profile. You
will have the opportunity to claim collected information relating to you and to change its visibility setting
or remove the information. However we cannot guarantee that we will not later collect from
publicly­available websites other information that pertains to you.
Cookies and Other Technology
The Services may use “cookies” and other technologies such as pixel tags and web beacons.
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers in the form of text files that are inserted and stored by your Web
browser on your computer’s hard drive. These technologies tell us which parts of our Sites you have
visited and how you use our Services. They are also used to analyze and improve the design and
functionality of our Services. If you choose to delete cookies from your device or block them from being
stored on your device, please note that the full functionality of the Services may not be available to you.
“Web beacons” are images embedded in a Web page or e­mail for the purpose of measuring and
analyzing Services usage and activity. We, or third­party service providers acting on our behalf, may use
Web beacons to help us analyze usage and improve our Services.
We may use third­party service providers to help us analyze certain online activities and improve our
Services. For example, these service providers may help us measure the performance of our online
campaigns or analyze visitor activity on the Sites. We may permit these service providers to use cookies
and other technologies to perform these services for us. We do not share any personal information about
our users with these third­party service providers, and these service providers do not collect such
information on our behalf. Our third­party service providers are not permitted to use information about
our users that they collect for us for any purpose other than providing services to us.
How We Use Information
We use the information we collect to provide, operate and improve our Services, respond to you, and
foster a positive user experience. Our Services include providing an online platform that connects
employers who have job openings with individuals who are seeking jobs.
By registering with Studio6, by managing your Anthology Account, or by opting in when presented with
choices, you have consented for us to use your information in the following ways:
     ●   to create a profile for you based on information that you have provided to us, information
         imported or collected from other sites or applications, or information provided to us by third
         parties;
     ●   to provide personalized, targeted, or location­based content, services, and advertising from us and
         third parties, including alerting you to relevant job openings;
     ●   to allow you to contact other users or to invite others to join or create a Anthology Account;
                                                        2

     ●   to allow you to import information about yourself or your contacts from other sites or applications
         or to export your information to other sites or applications;
     ●   to contact you about feature updates and informational and service­related communications,
         including important security updates;
     ●   to provide you with additional communications, information, and promotions such as newsletters
         and career advice;
     ●   to inform you of other products or services available from Studio6 or its affiliates;
     ●   to enable you to contact us and for us to respond to you to conduct surveys, promotions and
         contests, and to publish the results thereof;
     ●   to provide information about you and your potential interest in job postings to employers, as
         further described in this Privacy Policy and the Services;
     ●   to provide products and services to employers to complete the recruitment and hiring process;
     ●   to generate internal reports about the use of our Services;
     ●   to allow you to share jobs and profile information with your connections;
     ●   to give search engines access to public information;
     ●   to detect, investigate and prevent activities that may violate our policies or be illegal; and
     ●   to make suggestions and draw inferences about you. For example, we may make suggestions
         about additional jobs, products or services that might be of interest to you.
Information you post in public areas of the Services or make visible in the job candidate database may be
accessed, used, and stored by others around the world, including those in countries that might not have
legislation that guarantees adequate protection of personal information as defined by your country of
residence. We do not control these third parties and we are not responsible for their use of information
you give to us. Accordingly, you should not post sensitive information, or any other information you
would not want made public, to any public area.
Our Services may include the display of and notice to you of personalized products, content, and
advertising relating to your education, occupation, career history, skills and experience, awards,
memberships and affiliations, activities, interests or other information we have collected about you. We
use data we have about you to determine whether you might be interested in the opportunities, products or
services of a particular third party. We show you targeted ads online and may also email targeted ads.
These ads are targeted (or retargeted) based on information we collect about you and information about
you we acquire from third parties.​ How We Share Information
Our Services are designed to provide individuals with access to job openings and to provide employers
with referrals to job candidates. We may share information with third parties for their direct marketing
purposes unless you opt out of such disclosure. We disclose your information as set forth below:
1. We share your information with third parties who help deliver our Services to you. Examples include
hosting our web servers, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments,
and providing customer service. These companies will have access to your information as necessary to
perform their functions, but they may not use that data for any other purpose.
2. We may disclose information to third parties if you consent. For example:
(a) if you post a job opening and choose to make it public, we will disclose information about the job and
employer in our job openings database;
                                                        3

(b) if you express interest in a job opening, we will provide anonymous information from your Anthology
Account to the relevant employer;
(c) if you give us consent to disclose your name, contact details and other personal information to an
employer, we will provide that information to the employer;
(d) unless you opt out of receiving information about the opportunities, products, or services of third
parties, we supply your contact information to those third parties so they may contact you; or
(e) if you previously chose to receive newsletters, commercial e­mails or other communications from us
or third parties, but subsequently change your mind, you may opt out in those emails or by editing your
Anthology Account settings.
However, we will not disclose to employers or job candidates information in your Anthology Account
that is designated as non­public.
We may also aggregate data regarding job qualifications, education and professional qualifications, age,
experience level, salaries (including historic salary, salary ranges for a particular job posting and salary
expectations), Site and Services usage and other information. This aggregated data does not identify users
individually, and may be used by us for any business purposes and made available to third parties,
including employers, job candidates, investors, and the public.
3. We disclose information if legally required to do so, or at our discretion pursuant to a request from a
governmental entity or if we believe in good faith – after considering your privacy interests and other
factors – that such action is necessary to: (a) meet legal requirements or comply with legal process; (b)
protect our rights or property or our affiliated companies; (c) prevent a crime or protect national security;
or (d) protect the personal safety of users or the public.
4. We may disclose and transfer information to a third party who acquires any or all of Studio6’s
business, whether such acquisition is by way of merger, consolidation or purchase of all or a substantial
portion of our assets. In addition, in the event Studio6 becomes the subject of an insolvency proceeding,
such information will be disposed of in a transaction approved by the court. You will be notified of the
sale of all or a substantial portion of our business to a third party by email or through a prominent notice
posted on the Sites.
How We Store Information
Since we believe that managing your career is a life­long process, even if you close or deactivate your
Anthology Account we will retain all the information we gather about you so that your repeat use of our
Services is more efficient, practical and relevant until you change or remove your personal data as
described below. You may access, review, correct, update, change or delete your Anthology Account
information or résumé at any time. Log into your account, go to your personal information page or
résumé, and make the desired changes.
Access to or correction, update, or deletion of your personal information may be denied or limited by us if
it would violate another person’s rights and/or as otherwise permitted by applicable law. If you wish to
permanently delete or close your Anthology Account and all account information altogether, please
contact us at ​legal@anthology.co​  . We will send you an email to confirm that your personal information
                                                        4

has been deleted (other than archival copies which are not accessible by you or third parties on the
Internet and information that has been anonymized and aggregated with data from other users). The
archival copy is retained only for as long as needed for audit and record purposes. We will also keep logs
and information that may relate to your activity on the site. We may retain and continue to use
anonymized and aggregated information as long as we have a business purpose for doing so.
Account Security
The security of your Anthology Account relies on your protection of your password. You are responsible
for maintaining the security of your password. You are solely responsible for any and all activities that
occur under your Anthology Account. You may not share your password with anyone. We will never ask
you to send your password or other sensitive information to us in an email, though we may ask you to
enter it into the Services. Any email or other communication requesting your password, asking you to
provide sensitive account information via email, or linking to a website with a URL that does not begin
with ​http://www.anthology.co​   should be treated as unauthorized and suspicious and should be reported to
us immediately at ​ legal@anthology.co​ . If you do share your password with a third party for any reason,
the third party will have access to your Anthology Account and your information, and you are responsible
for actions taken using your password. If you believe someone else has obtained access to your password,
please change it immediately by logging in to your Anthology Account and using the password change
feature. If you believe that an unauthorized access has already occurred please report it immediately
at ​
   legal@anthology.co​  .We may have access to your password and may use such password to access your
account for debugging, quality assurance, or other internal purposes.
Security of the Services
We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the information submitted to us, both during
transmission and once we receive it. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect
your personal information, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage,
is 100% secure and we cannot guarantee its absolute security. In the event of an inadvertent disclosure of
your personal information we will take all commercially reasonable steps to limit and remedy the
disclosure as required by the applicable law. If you have any questions about the security of our Services,
you can contact us via email or telephone at ​ legal@anthology.co​ or (206) 569­5188.
Children
The Services are not intended for, nor do we knowingly collect information from, children under the age
of majority. Consistent with the federal Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we
will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without
requiring parental consent. Any person who provides his or her personal information to us through our
Services represents that he or she is 13 years of age or older.
International Visitors
The Services are hosted in and provided from the United States. If you use our Services from the
European Union, Canada or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ
from United States law, please note that you are transferring your personal data to the United States. The
United States does not have the same data protection laws as the European Union, Canada and some other
                                                       5

regions. By providing your personal information, you consent to the transfer of your personal data to the
United States and the use of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
Referrals
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our Services or a job position, we will ask
you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one­time email
inviting him or her to visit the Services. We store this information for the sole purpose of sending this
one­time email and tracking the success of our referral program, and do not use this information for any
other marketing purpose unless we obtain consent from that person or we explicitly say otherwise. Please
be aware that when you use any send­to­a­friend functionality through our Services, your name and
e­mail address may be included in the communication sent to your friend.
How We Respond To Do Not Track Signals
Please note that your browser settings may allow you to automatically transmit a “Do Not Track” signal
to websites and online services you visit. There is no consensus among industry participants as to what
“Do Not Track” means in this context. Like many websites and online services, we do not alter our
practices when we receive a “Do Not Track” signal from a visitor’s browser. To find out more about “Do
Not Track”, please visit ​ http://www.allaboutdnt.com​  .
California Residents ­ Your CA Privacy Rights
Pursuant to California Civil Code Section 1798.83, residents of the State of California have the right to
request from companies conducting business in California a list of all third parties to which Studio6 has
disclosed certain categories of personal information during the preceding year for the third parties’ direct
marketing purposes and the categories of personal information Studio6 shares. Alternatively, the law
provides that a company that has a privacy policy that provides consumers choice (opt­out or opt­in)
regarding sharing personal information with third parties for those third parties’ direct marketing purposes
may instead provide information on how to exercise that choice. Studio6 qualifies for the alternative
option; it has a comprehensive privacy policy that sets forth that Studio6 provides you choice prior to
sharing your personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. If you choose to
opt­out at the time Studio6 offers that choice, Studio6 does not share your information with that identified
third party for its direct marketing purposes.
If you are a California resident and you have questions about our practices with respect to sharing
information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes and your ability to exercise choice,
please send your request to the following email address: ​  legal@anthology.co​  or write to us at the
following mailing address: 209 1/2 First Ave South, Suite 302, Seattle, WA 98104. You must put the
statement “Your California Privacy Rights” in the subject field of your e­mail or include it in your writing
if you choose to write to us at the designated mailing address. You must include your name, street
address, city, state, and zip code. We are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly,
or do not have complete information.
Changes to Privacy Policy
If we decide to materially change the substance of this Privacy Policy, we will, where required, contact
you via the email address that you maintain in your Anthology Account. We will also post those changes
through a prominent notice on the Sites.
                                                        6

Contact Information
If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at ​
                                                                                  legal@anthology.co​
                                                                                                    . We
will use reasonable efforts to promptly answer your question or resolve your problem.
                                                    7
